[
{"question":"1. Constant head method is suitable for _________ type of soils",
"answers":{
            "a":"Coarse grained soils",
            "b":"Fine grained soils",
            "c":"Cohesive soils",
            "d":"Cohesion less soils"
          },
"correctAnswer":"a"},

{"question":"2. Variable head test is suitable for _______ type of soils",
"answers":{
            "a":"Coarse grained soils",
            "b":"Fine grained soils",
            "c":"Cohesive soils",
            "d":"Cohesion less soils"
          },
"correctAnswer":"b"}, 

{"question":"3. Which test is used to find the coefficient of permeability of a partially saturated soil",
"answers":{
            "a":"Constant head method",
            "b":"Variable head test",
            "c":"Capillary permeability test",
            "d":"Consolidation test data"
          },
 "correctAnswer":"c"},

{"question":"4. For a fully saturated soil ______ is the permeability",
"answers":{
            "a":"More",
            "b":"Less",
            "c":"Zero",
            "d":"Both a and b"
          },
"correctAnswer":"a"},

{"question":"5. Coefficient of permeability by variable head test is given by",
"answers":{
            "a":"k=al/At ln(h1/h2)",
            "b":"k=a/At ln(h2/h1)",
            "c":"k=al/At ln(h2/h1)",
            "d":"k=a/At ln(h1/h2)"
          },
"correctAnswer":"a"},

{"question":"6. If size of the particle increases 2 times then K increases to ",
"answers":{
            "a":"4 Times",
            "b":"2 Times",
            "c":"Decreases",
            "d":"Remains same"
          },
"correctAnswer":"a"},

{"question":"7. Soil with largest void ratio have ______permeability",
"answers":{
            "a":"Less",
            "b":"More",
            "c":"Equal",
            "d":"Zero"
          },
"correctAnswer":"a"},

{"question":"8. Due to change of temperature, the ᵞw and µ of the liquid reduced by 10% and 40% respectively. What is the change in the permeability of the soil ",
"answers":{
            "a":"Reduces by 10%",
            "b":"Reduces by 90%",
            "c":"Reduces by 40%",
            "d":"Both a and b"
          },
"correctAnswer":"d"},

{"question":"9. Permeable soil has a K (cm/sec)value of ",
"answers":{
            "a":"> 0.1",
            "b":"< 0",
            "c":"=0",
            "d":"None"
          },
"correctAnswer":"a"},

{"question":"10. Coefficient of permeability is also called as",
"answers":{
            "a":"Hydraulic conductivity",
            "b":"Conductivity",
            "c":"Energy of water",
            "d":"Potential of water"
          },
"correctAnswer":"a"}


]
